{
    "subject": "resource/Blue_Jasmine",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Woody_Allen",
    "human_readable": "The director of Blue Jasmine is Woody Allen.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8632366061210632,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Blue Jasmine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6552767753601074,
            "question": "What themes are explored in Woody Allen's films like Blue Jasmine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6171401143074036,
            "question": "Has Woody Allen won any awards for his work on Blue Jasmine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5671932697296143,
            "question": "Woody Allen has directed many movies. Can you name another one?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5392507314682007,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors that starred in Blue Jasmine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4042724370956421,
            "question": "What is the plot of Blue Jasmine about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35190650820732117,
            "question": "Is Blue Jasmine a comedy or a drama?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3209127187728882,
            "question": "Where was Blue Jasmine filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29098978638648987,
            "question": "What year was Blue Jasmine released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0513223372399807,
            "question": "What is the name of the director known for films like Annie Hall and Midnight in Paris?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of Blue Jasmine is Woody Allen.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8833_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Blue Jasmine released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8833_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Blue Jasmine filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8833_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Blue Jasmine a comedy or a drama?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8833_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8833_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8833_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8833_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8833_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8833_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8833_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8833_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8833_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8833_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8833_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that \"Blue Jasmine was directed by the renowned filmmaker Woody Allen\" and \"Blue Jasmine is a 2013 American drama film written and directed by Woody Allen,\" which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}